pxlvlt.com 2013-08-13

# Adperio Privacy Statement

Adperio Privacy Statement
Revised: September 2009
Collection of Your Personal Information
Use of Your Personal Information
Use of Cookies
Use of Web Beacons
Sharing of Your Personal Information
Accessing Your Personal Information
Communication Preferences
Security
Changes to This Privacy Statement
Contacting Us
It is important that you fully understand what happens to the information we gather from you as a
publisher, advertiser or other user of Adperio’s website and services. Please read this Privacy Statement
carefully to understand how we will use and protect your personal information.
Collection of Your Personal Information
Upon registration we will ask a publisher to provide personal information such as name, email address,
physical mailing address, phone number, taxpayer ID number, or a faxed copy of a government-issued
ID. We may also collect non-personal information, such as your zip code, the amount you spend on
advertising, what type of Internet traffic you have (incentive versus non-incentive), or the source of your
Internet traffic (web versus email or search). We may use this non-personal data to improve the services
and advertising content we provide to you as well as tailor the services provided to you. We may also
share this non-personal information with others, such as interested advertisers, in aggregate,
anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personal information about
you or any other person.
When you receive email from Adperio, we may use Web beacons and customized links (or similar
technologies) to determine whether the email has been opened and whether you clicked on a link in the
email in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.
back to top
Use of Your Personal Information
Adperio collects and uses your personal information and other data to operate and improve our
services. These uses may include providing you with more effective affiliate management service;
making our Site easier to use; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our services; and
providing you with content and communication that are relevant to your business objectives.
We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may contact you via email with
account information, with announcements that new advertising content is available for you, or with
responses to inquiries you make with the affiliate management team or other company representatives.

For more information about the use of information for communication, see the Communication
Preference section below.
back to top
Use of Cookies
A “cookie” is a small piece of data we store on your hard drive. When you logon to our Site using your
email address and password, we place a cookie on your hard drive. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked
to any personal information while on our site. A cookie is used for convenience, and allows you to move
from page to page of the password-protected portion of our Site without having to login again on each
page. Once you logout, these cookies are deleted from your computer.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but,
if you prefer, you can usually change your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline
cookies on our Site, you may still use our Site, however you may have difficulty navigating through the
password-protected portion of our Site.
Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which
means they cannot be used to track your movements around the Web.
back to top
Use of Web Beacons
Web beacons, also known as clear gifs, single-pixel gifs, pixel tags, or action tags, are tiny electronic
images that we may use in our email communication to let us know if you have opened an email that we
sent you or clicked on a link within that email.
back to top
Sharing of Your Personal Information
Except as described in this statement or in any agreement that you enter with us, we will not disclose
your personal information without your consent. Adperio may disclose personal information if required
to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property
or personal safety of Adperio and our affiliates, both publishers and advertisers. Your personal
information and other data may be transferred in connection with a business transition, such as a
merger, acquisition, insolvency, or asset sale.
In order to provide our products and services, we may hire other companies to provide limited services
on our behalf, such as to send email, to perform statistical analysis of our services, to provide affiliate
support, to carry out invoicing, or to make payments. These service providers will be permitted to obtain
only the personal information they need to perform their functions. They are required to maintain the
confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.
Our website contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, please consult those
sites' individual privacy statements in order to determine how they treat user information. Adperio is

not responsible for the privacy statements or the content of such sites, and the privacy practices of
other Websites and companies are not covered by this statement. We request that users report any and
all concerns about our business partners' privacy practices directly to us as outlined in the Contacting Us
section below.
back to top
Accessing Your Personal Information
Adperio publishers are able to change their personal information at any time. The fastest way to change
personal information is to logon to your Adperio account and go to the Account Info area, then click
“Edit Account.” If for some reason this page does not work, or you have any questions, you may contact
us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below. Advertisers and other website users may change their
personal information that we collect by contacting us as outlined in the Contacting Us section below.
back to top
Communication Preferences
If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you may opt out at any time. These
choices do not apply to the receipt of specific administrative notices that are required by law,
regulation, or as needed to service your account.
If you do not wish to receive email messages, you may opt out by clicking on the “SafeUnsubscribe™”
link at the bottom of any marketing email. Opt out requests made through the “SafeUnsubscribe™” link
are processed immediately.
back to top
Security
Adperio is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of
security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access,
use, or disclosure. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted
access to your personal information, such as our accounting department accessing your payment
information in order to send you your publisher commission payment. Our employees must use
password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desks. When they return, they must re-enter
their password to regain access.
A password is used to help protect your account and personal information. It is your responsibility to
keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a
computer with anyone you should always logout before leaving our Site or service to protect access to
your information from subsequent users. If you feel your password has been compromised, you should
change it immediately. After you have finished using our Site, you should logout of your Adperio account
and close your browser so that no unauthorized persons can use our Site under your name and account
information.
back to top

Changes to This Privacy Statement
We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services. When we post
changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. We
encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Adperio is using and
protecting your information.
back to top
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy at Adperio, please contact us by clicking here,
or you may contact us in writing at:
Adperio
Attn: Privacy Department
2000 S. Colorado Blvd. Tower 1, Suite 7000
Denver, CO 80222
